Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Treasurer's Office records, 1916-1949 and undated RL.11720
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accounts--Active, Inactive and Discontinued, 1921-1944 and undated; 2
  - Northern Pacific Rail Road, undated (Reel 87)
  - Norwich Pharmacal, undated (Reel 76)
  - Norwich Pharmacal, undated (Reel 87)
  - Noxon Chemical Products, undated (Reel 76)
  - Old Dominion Garment, undated (Reel 76)
  - Old Witch (formerly United Ammonia), undated (Reel 76)
  - Old Witch (formerly United Ammonia), undated (Reel 87)
  - Omar Mills & Bakeries (see National Baking), undated (Reel 76)
  - Omar Mills & Bakeries (see National Baking), undated (Reel 87)
  - Orange Crush, 1933-1937 (Reel 535)
  - Orange Crush, undated (Reel 87)
  - Osborn Manufacturing (Chicago), undated (Reel 76)
  - Osborn Manufacturing (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - O'Sullivan Rubber, undated (Reel 76)
  - Overseas Motor Service, undated (Reel 87)
  - Pabst Dietary Products, undated (Reel 76)
  - Pabst Dietary Products, undated (Reel 87)
  - Pacific American Fisheries, undated (Reel 87)
  - Pacific Coast Electrical Bureau (San Francisco), undated (Reel 76)
  - Pacific Coast Electrical Bureau (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - Papier, Poudre (London), undated (Reel 76)
  - Parfumerie St. Denis, undated (Reel 76)
  - Parfumerie St. Denis, undated (Reel 87)
  - Parker Meyer Dennis (Chicago), undated (Reel 76)
  - Parker Meyer Dennis (Chicago), undated (Reel 87)
  - Parker-Regan (San Francisco), undated (Reel 76)
  - Parker-Regan (San Francisco), undated (Reel 87)
  - Park-Lexington, undated (Reel 76)
  - Park-Lexington, undated (Reel 87)
  - Pennsylvania Rail Road, undated (Reel 76)
  - Pennsylvania Rail Road, undated (Reel 88)
  - Pennsylvania Rubber, undated (Reel 76)
  - Pennsylvania Rubber, undated (Reel 88)
  - Permutit, undated (Reel 76)
  - Permutit, undated (Reel 88)
  - Peter Cailler (Kohler Swiss Chocolates), undated (Reel 76)
  - Peter Henderson & Co., undated (Reel 75)
  - Peter Henderson & Co., undated (Reel 87)
  - Phoenix Hosiery, undated (Reel 81)
  - Phoenix Hosiery, undated (Reel 88)
  - Pictorial Review, undated (Reel 76)
  - Piel Bros., undated (Reel 76)
  - Piel Bros., undated (Reel 88)
  - Piggly Wiggly, undated (Reel 76)
  - Piggly Wiggly, undated (Reel 88)
  - Pin-Ap-Ola, undated (Reel 88)
  - Pinaud, undated (Reel 76)
  - Pinaud, undated (Reel 88)
  - Pineapple Producers Cooperative Association, undated (Reel 76)
  - Pineapple Producers Cooperative Association, undated (Reel 88)
  - Plush Association, undated (Reel 88)
  - Pond's, 1929-1933 (Reel 535)
  - Portland Cement Association, undated (Reel 76)
  - Portland Cement Association, undated (Reel 88)
  - Postum Cereal, undated (Reel 76)
    Calumet-Certo, Baker's Coconut, Richard Hellman Mayonnaise, Maxwell House
  - Postum Cereal, undated (Reel 88)
  - President Suspender (Boston), undated (Reel 76)
  - President Suspender (Boston), undated (Reel 88)
  - Printz Biederman, undated (Reel 76)
  - Printz Biederman, undated (Reel 88)
  - Pronunciphone (Chicago), undated (Reel 76)
  - Purchase sales: foreign exchange, 1933-1940 (Reel 536)
  - Quaker Lace, undated (Reel 76)
  - Quaker Oats, undated (Reel 76)
  - Radio Manufacturers Association, undated (Reel 76)
  - Radio Manufacturers Association, undated (Reel 88)
  - Railway Express Agency, undated (Reel 76)
  - Railway Express Agency, undated (Reel 88)
  - Rand McNally, undated (Reel 76)
  - Rand McNally, undated (Reel 88)
  - Rayon Institute of America, undated (Reel 76)
  - Rayon Institute of America, undated (Reel 88)
  - Real Silk Hosiery Mills (Chicago), undated (Reel 76)
  - Real Silk Hosiery Mills (Chicago), undated (Reel 88)
  - Reliance Property Management (S.W. Straus & Co.), undated (Reel 76)
  - Reliance Property Management (S.W. Straus & Co.), undated (Reel 88)
  - Remington Rand, undated (Reel 88)
  - Rice Schmidt Baking, undated (Reel 76)
  - Rice Schmidt Baking, undated (Reel 88)
  - Richardson (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 76)
  - Richardson (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 88)
  - Richman Brothers (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 76)
  - Richman Brothers (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 88)
  - Ritz Carlton Hotel, undated (Reel 81)
  - Robert Gair, undated (Reel 74)
  - Robeson Rochester, undated (Reel 77)
  - Robeson Rochester, undated (Reel 88)
  - Roma Wine (San Francisco), undated (Reel 77)
  - Roma Wine (San Francisco), undated (Reel 88)
  - Rowntrees Ltd., undated (Reel 77)
  - S. Sternau, undated (Reel 50)
  - S. Sternau, undated (Reel 77)
  - S.W. Straus & Co., undated (Reel 77)
  - Salerno-Megowen Biscuit (Chicago), undated (Reel 77)
  - Salerno-Megowen Biscuit (Chicago), undated (Reel 88)
  - Sardine Fisheries of Maine, undated (Reel 77)
  - Sardine Fisheries of Maine, undated (Reel 88)
  - Savage Arms, undated (Reel 77)
  - Savings & Loan Corporation Advertisers (U.S. Building & Loan League), undated (Reel 77)
  - Savings & Loan Corporation Advertisers (U.S. Building & Loan League), undated (Reel 88)
  - Scholl Manufacturing (Chicago), undated (Reel 77)
  - Schweizer Importers, undated (Reel 88)
  - Seacoast Canning, undated (Reel 88)
  - Sealed Container, undated (Reel 77)
  - Sealed Container, undated (Reel 88)
  - Sealtest System Laboratories, undated (Reel 88)
  - Seamless Rubber, undated (Reel 77)
  - Seattle Loan & Discount, 1938 (Reel 536)
  - Seeck & Kade (Pertussin), undated (Reel 81)
  - Seth Thomas Clock, undated (Reel 77)
  - Seth Thomas Clock, undated (Reel 88)
  - Shell (San Francisco), 1928-1936 (Reel 535)
  - Shell Outdoor Advertising, 1936 (Reel 535)
  - Shell Petroleum (St. Louis), 1930-1936 (Reel 535)
  - Shell Service (Van Fleet & Durkee), 1931 (Reel 535)
  - Shell--Figures for Justice Department, 1941 (Reel 535)
  - Shell--Radio program, 1935 (Reel 535)
  - Shultz Brands, undated (Reel 77)
  - Shultz Brands, undated (Reel 88)
  - Silvikrin (hair tonic; C.F. Ferratte, Wettingen, Switzerland), undated (Reel 81)
  - Simmons, undated (Reel 77)
  - Simmons, undated (Reel 88)
  - Skinner Organ, undated (Reel 77)
  - Skinner Organ, undated (Reel 88)
  - Smokador Manufacturing, undated (Reel 77)
  - Smokador Manufacturing, undated (Reel 88)
  - Societe Europeene de Publicite, undated (Reel 88)
  - Society for Electrical Development, undated (Reel 77)
  - Society for Electrical Development, undated (Reel 88)
  - Society of American Florists and Ornamental Horticulturists, undated (Reel 81)
  - Society of American Florists and Ornamental Horticulturists, undated (Reel 88)
  - Sonatone, undated (Reel 88)
  - Sonora Phonograph, undated (Reel 77)
  - Sonora Phonograph, undated (Reel 88)
  - Sonotone, undated (Reel 77)
  - Sperry Flour (San Francisco), undated (Reel 77)
  - Sperry Flour (San Francisco), undated (Reel 88)
  - Spry (Sternau), undated (Reel 77)
  - Stanco, undated (Reel 88)
  - Standard Brands, undated (Reel 88)
  - Standard Brands: Fleischmann's Yeast, 1930-1936 (Reel 535)
  - Standard Brands: Royal Baking Powder, 1923-1938 (Reel 535)
  - Standard Brands: Widler, undated (Reel 535)
  - Standard Brands: Yeast for Health, 1930-1936 (Reel 535)
  - Stanley Insulating (Boston), undated (Reel 77)
  - Stanley Insulating (Boston), undated (Reel 88)
  - Sterling Varnish, undated (Reel 77)
  - Stewart Phonograph, undated (Reel 77)
  - Sun Maid Raisin Growers Association (San Francisco), undated (Reel 77)
  - Sun Maid Raisin Growers Association (San Francisco), undated (Reel 88)
  - Swift, 1921-1933 (Reel 536)
  - Swift, 1929 and undated (Reel 77)
  - Tea Garden Products, undated (Reel 81)
  - Tea Garden Products, undated (Reel 88)
  - Tested Products Laboratories (Placidau-United Drug), undated (Reel 77)
  - Tested Products Laboratories (Placidau-United Drug), undated (Reel 88)
  - Tex-O-Kan Flour Mills (St. Louis), undated (Reel 77)
  - Tex-O-Kan Flour Mills (St. Louis), undated (Reel 88)
  - Thermoid Rubber, undated (Reel 77)
  - Thomas Young Nurseries, undated (Reel 78)
  - Thomas Young Nurseries, undated (Reel 88)
  - Thompson-Koch, undated (Reel 88)
  - Tide Water Oil, undated (Reel 77)
  - Time, undated (Reel 88)
  - Time (and Fortune), undated (Reel 77)
  - Time Plan, 1941 (Reel 536)
  - Todd Shipyards, 1943 (Reel 536)
  - Toledo Scale, undated (Reel 77)
  - Toledo Scale, undated (Reel 88)
  - Town House (San Francisco), undated (Reel 77)
  - Town House (San Francisco), undated (Reel 88)
  - Traveler's Credit, 1939-1940 (Reel 536)
  - Tromite, undated (Reel 77)
  - Turner & Walls, undated (Reel 77)
  - Turner & Walls, undated (Reel 88)
  - U.S. Industrial Alcohol, undated (Reel 50)
  - U.S. Industrial Alcohol, undated (Reel 77)
  - U.S. Rubber, undated (Reel 50)
  - U.S. Rubber, undated (Reel 77)
  - Union Tobacco, undated (Reel 77)
  - Union Tobacco, undated (Reel 88)
  - United Air Lines Transport, undated (Reel 81)
  - United Air Lines Transport, undated (Reel 88)
  - United Autographic Register (Chicago), undated (Reel 77)
  - United Autographic Register (Chicago), undated (Reel 88)
  - United Dressed Beef Council (Swift), 1933 (Reel 536)
  - United Motors, undated (Reel 88)
  - United States Industrial Alcohol, undated (Reel 88)
  - United States Rubber, undated (Reel 88)
  - Urbana Wine, undated (Reel 50)
  - Urbana Wine, undated (Reel 77)
  - Urbana Wine, undated (Reel 88)
  - Vanadium Corporation of America, undated (Reel 77)
  - Vanity Fair Silk Mills, undated (Reel 88)
  - Varney Air Service (San Francisco), undated (Reel 77)
  - Vaughan's Seed Store, undated (Reel 88)
  - Vauv, undated (Reel 50)
  - Vauv (Chicago), undated (Reel 77)
  - W.A. Taylor, 1941 (Reel 536)
  - W.H. & A.E. Margerison & Co., undated (Reel 87)
  - Wadsworth Watch Case, undated (Reel 81)
  - Ward-Stilson (Chicago), undated (Reel 77)
  - Warner Chemical, undated (Reel 77)
  - Warner Chemical, undated (Reel 88)
  - Washington State Progress Commission, 1937-1941 (Reel 536)
  - Washington State Progress Commission, undated (Reel 88)
  - WBBM Broadcasting (Chicago), undated (Reel 77)
  - WBBM Broadcasting (Chicago), undated (Reel 88)
  - Welch's Grape Juice, undated (Reel 50)
  - Welch's Grape Juice, undated (Reel 78)
  - Welch's Grape Juice, undated (Reel 88)
  - Western, undated (Reel 88)
  - Western (Chicago), undated (Reel 78)
  - Western Air Express (Los Angeles), undated (Reel 78)
  - Western Air Express (Los Angeles), undated (Reel 88)
  - Western Growers Protective Association (Los Angeles), undated (Reel 78)
  - Western Tablet & Stationery (Chicago), undated (Reel 78)
  - Western Tablet & Stationery (Chicago), undated (Reel 88)
  - Wheeler-Osgood (San Francisco), undated (Reel 78)
  - Wheeler-Osgood (San Francisco), undated (Reel 88)
  - Wilcolator, undated (Reel 78)
  - William Carter, undated (Reel 73)
  - William Hollins & Co., undated (Reel 75)
  - Williams & Cunningham (Chicago), undated (Reel 78)
  - Williams Health System (San Francisco), undated (Reel 78)
  - Williams Health System (San Francisco), undated (Reel 88)
  - Williams-Marvin (San Francisco), undated (Reel 78)
  - Williamson Heater (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 78)
  - Winchester Repeating Arms, undated (Reel 88)
  - Wine Advisory Board, 1939-1940 (Reel 536)
  - Witt Fillmore (Cincinnati), undated (Reel 74)
  - Wm. R. Warner, undated (Reel 50)
  - Wm. R. Warner, undated (Reel 77)
    Iredell-Hodgman matter
  - Wm. R. Warner, undated (Reel 78)
  - Wm. Wrigley, undated (Reel 50)
  - Wm. Wrigley, undated (Reel 78)
  - Wohl Shoe (St. Louis), undated (Reel 78)
  - Wohl Shoe (St. Louis), undated (Reel 88)
  - Wood Office Furniture Associates, undated (Reel 78)
  - Wood Office Furniture Associates, undated (Reel 88)
  - Zenith Radio, undated (Reel 78)
  - Zenith Radio, undated (Reel 88)
- Foreign Offices--Group Insurance, 1932-1941; 3
  - Alexandria, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Antwerp, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Barcelona/Madrid, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Batavia, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Berlin, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Bombay (Mumbai), 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Bucharest, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Buenos Aires, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Canada, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Copenhagen, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - Johannesburg, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - London, 1932-1941 (Reel 69)
  - London, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Melbourne, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Milan, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Paris, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Sao Paulo, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Stockholm, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Sydney, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Warsaw, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
  - Wellington, 1932-1941 (Reel 70)
- Former Stock Holders, undated; 4
  - A.E. Hartzell, undated (Reel 78)
  - A.V. Pollock, undated (Reel 80)
  - Albert Burwinkle, undated (Reel 79)
  - Albert Leffingwell, undated (Reel 79)
  - Alberta Hays, undated (Reel 79)
  - Alette Kron, undated (Reel 80)
  - Alice Lee, undated (Reel 79)
  - Alice Peddrick Haupt, undated (Reel 79)
  - Alice Wakefield, undated (Reel 80)
  - Ann De Barry, undated (Reel 79)
  - Anne Juenker, undated (Reel 79)
  - Anthony Grubb, undated (Reel 79)
  - Antony Stanford, undated (Reel 80)
  - Arthur Deerson, undated (Reel 78)
  - Austin Thomas, undated (Reel 80)
  - C. Frederic Bell, undated (Reel 79)
  - C.A. Posey, undated (Reel 79)
  - C.C. Seedorf, undated (Reel 79)
  - C.O. Woodbury, undated (Reel 79)
  - Carl McQuinn, undated (Reel 79)
  - Catherine Clancy, undated (Reel 78)
  - Catherine Schibeck, undated (Reel 80)
  - Charles Austin, undated (Reel 79)
  - Charles Christoph, undated (Reel 79)
  - Charline Davenport, undated (Reel 78)
  - Chester Du Close, undated (Reel 78)
  - David Graham, undated (Reel 79)
  - Dorothy Casey, undated (Reel 79)
  - Dorothy Lutz, undated (Reel 79)
  - Dudley Fay, undated (Reel 79)
  - Dudley Mudge, undated (Reel 79)
  - Dwight Cook, undated (Reel 79)
  - E.H. Knott, undated (Reel 80)
  - Earle Clark, undated (Reel 79)
  - Edmund Pitts, undated (Reel 80)
  - Edward Fuller, undated (Reel 79)
  - Edward Gardner, undated (Reel 78)
  - Edward Gardner, undated (Reel 79)
  - Edward Gordon, undated (Reel 79)
  - Edward Hungness, undated (Reel 79)
  - Edward Pratt, undated (Reel 79)
  - Eleanor Hunter, undated (Reel 79)
  - Eleanor Record Sigel, undated (Reel 80)
  - Elizabeth Devree, undated (Reel 79)
  - Elma Hunt, undated (Reel 79)
  - Elsie Ogbert, undated (Reel 79)
  - Elsy Brandt (Stephens) Joslyn, undated (Reel 80)
  - Emil Hackbarth Jr., undated (Reel 78)
  - Emma Herbers, undated (Reel 78)
  - Ethel Schaffer, undated (Reel 80)
  - Ewing Webb, undated (Reel 80)
  - F.J. McArdie, undated (Reel 80)
  - Florence West, undated (Reel 79)
  - Frank Gerard, undated (Reel 78)
  - Frank Whalen, undated (Reel 80)
  - Frank Woodruff, undated (Reel 80)
  - Frederic Wurzburg, undated (Reel 80)
  - G.T. Peterson, undated (Reel 80)
  - George Faulkner, undated (Reel 79)
  - Grace McMaster, undated (Reel 80)
  - Harold Stansbury, undated (Reel 79)
  - Harry Froede, undated (Reel 79)
  - Helen Butter, undated (Reel 79)
  - Helen Doane, undated (Reel 79)
  - Helen Ochocki, undated (Reel 80)
  - Helen Thompson, undated (Reel 79)
  - Helena Williams, undated (Reel 79)
  - Helene Goggin, undated (Reel 79)
  - Helene Spear Burr, undated (Reel 79)
  - Henry Legler, undated (Reel 80)
  - Herbert Polesie, undated (Reel 80)
  - Herschel Williams Jr., undated (Reel 80)
  - Ilma Bruno, undated (Reel 79)
  - Irene Tellon, undated (Reel 80)
  - J. Mae Dwyer, undated (Reel 79)
  - J. Sterling Getchell, undated (Reel 78)
  - James Hook Jr., undated (Reel 79)
  - James Kennedy Jr., undated (Reel 80)
  - James Mella, undated (Reel 80)
  - James Saville Yates, undated (Reel 79)
  - James Totten, undated (Reel 80)
  - Janet Cunningham, undated (Reel 79)
  - Janet Ettinger, undated (Reel 79)
  - Johanna Jarmus, undated (Reel 79)
  - John Christ, undated (Reel 79)
  - John Cohane, undated (Reel 79)
  - John Derries, undated (Reel 78)
  - John Esty, undated (Reel 78)
  - John Howard, undated (Reel 79)
  - John Maloy, undated (Reel 79)
  - John Schwarting, undated (Reel 80)
  - John Sorenson, undated (Reel 80)
  - John Van Zant, undated (Reel 79)
  - John Watson, undated (Reel 80)
  - Jorge Ruiz Palmer, undated (Reel 80)
  - Joseph D'Aleo, undated (Reel 78)
  - Joseph Griffitts, undated (Reel 79)
  - Julian Watkins, undated (Reel 80)
  - Karl Knipe, undated (Reel 80)
  - Katherine Lyford, undated (Reel 80)
  - Kathleen Bowker, undated (Reel 79)
  - L. Gordon Thompson, undated (Reel 80)
  - Laura Parry, undated (Reel 80)
  - Louis Grossman, undated (Reel 79)
  - Lucille Batchelder, undated (Reel 79)
  - Lucretia Bunel, undated (Reel 79)
  - Lydia Goedecke, undated (Reel 78)
  - Lynn McManus, undated (Reel 80)
  - M.E. Holmes, undated (Reel 78)
  - Mabel Hafner, undated (Reel 78)
  - Margaret Heavey, undated (Reel 78)
  - Margaret McLaughlin, undated (Reel 80)
  - Maria Candia, undated (Reel 79)
  - Marjorie Allen, undated (Reel 79)
  - Marthe Ketelson, undated (Reel 80)
  - Marvin Knight, undated (Reel 80)
  - Mary Bernice Hubsch, undated (Reel 79)
  - Mary Graves, undated (Reel 79)
  - Mary Louise Boykin, undated (Reel 79)
  - Mary Louise Boykin, undated (Reel 79)
  - Maurine Reed, undated (Reel 80)
  - May Olsen Smith, undated (Reel 80)
  - Melissa Taggert Doran, undated (Reel 79)
  - Melvin Woodworth, undated (Reel 80)
  - Milton Blair, undated (Reel 79)
  - Miss Rebecca Hourwich, undated (Reel 79)
  - Mrs. E. Gillespie, undated (Reel 78)
  - Mrs. Grace Hunt, undated (Reel 79)
  - Nan Findlow, undated (Reel 79)
  - Osgood Lovekin, undated (Reel 80)
  - Parker Holmes, undated (Reel 79)
  - Paul Cherington, undated (Reel 78)
  - Paul Harper, undated (Reel 79)
  - Paul Van Kavelaar, undated (Reel 79)
  - R. Lynn Baker, undated (Reel 79)
  - Raymond Brown, undated (Reel 79)
  - Richard Dunne, undated (Reel 78)
  - Richard James, undated (Reel 79)
  - Richmond Watson, undated (Reel 80)
  - Robert Flood, undated (Reel 78)
  - Robert Lewis, undated (Reel 80)
  - Robert MacKinnon, undated (Reel 79)
  - Robert Simon, undated (Reel 80)
  - Rose Gronsbell, undated (Reel 79)
  - Russell Pierce, undated (Reel 80)
  - Ruth Lieb, undated (Reel 80)
  - Ruth Siefkin, undated (Reel 80)
  - S.B. and Louise A. Galey, undated (Reel 79)
  - S.W. Benson, undated (Reel 79)
  - Samuel Moore, undated (Reel 80)
  - Sara Howard, undated (Reel 79)
  - Seymour Soule, undated (Reel 79)
  - Sherman Ellis, undated (Reel 78)
  - Shirley Warde, undated (Reel 80)
  - Stephen Itzenhauser, undated (Reel 79)
  - Stuart Cowan, undated (Reel 79)
  - T. Russell Paulson, undated (Reel 80)
  - Thomas Harrison, undated (Reel 79)
  - Thomas Hill, undated (Reel 78)
  - Thomas Morton, undated (Reel 80)
  - V.C. Hart, undated (Reel 79)
  - Vernon Churchill, undated (Reel 78)
  - Virginia Wylly, undated (Reel 80)
  - W. Stanfield Cooper, undated (Reel 79)
  - W. Stanley Holt, undated (Reel 79)
  - Wade Wieden, undated (Reel 80)
  - Walter O'Meara, undated (Reel 79)
  - Walter Resor, undated (Reel 80)
  - Wilfred Edie, undated (Reel 79)
  - Will Nyland, undated (Reel 79)
  - William Cormier, undated (Reel 79)
  - William Ferguson, undated (Reel 78)
  - William Griffin Jr., undated (Reel 79)
  - William Herrington, undated (Reel 79)
  - William Irwin, undated (Reel 79)
- Lawsuits, Claims, Court Orders, Judgments, etc., 1927-1944 and undated; 5
  - Accident--Iva Lindsey (coffee survey), 1940 (Reel 249)
  - Adele Kelly, undated (Reel 128)
  - Alex Kenne, undated (Reel 128)
  - Alfred Weeks, undated (Reel 128)
  - Andrew Jergens, undated (Reel 88)
  - Andrew Jergens--King v. Winchell, 1935 (Reel 66)
    See reel 75, diiscontinued accounts
  - Andrew Jergens--NBC, 1935 (Reel 66)
    See reel 88, signed releases
  - Andrew Jergens--Walter Winchell, Fletcher & Ellis, Gooderhaus & Worts, 1935 (Reel 66)
    See also reel 88
  - Anthony Mella, undated (Reel 128)
  - Ballantine--Austin McSweeney claim, Man in Hammock, 1941 (Reel 249)
  - Ballantine--Liflander claim, 1941 (Reel 249)
  - Ben Batsford general release (Royal and Nestle advertising), 1936 (Reel 88)
  - Ben Batsford v. JWT (Standard Brands, Nestle), 1934-1936 (Reel 66)
  - Bernie Foyer, undated (Reel 128)
  - Breed Abbott & Morgan--Compensation regarding income tax review, 1918-1928 (Reel 86)
  - Cartoon Films (contract proposal), 1937-1938 (Reel 86)
  - Charles Conroy, undated (Reel 128)
  - Chicago Office unpaid accounts, 1937-1938 (Reel 248)
  - Clarence Hornung--Claim, 1928 (Reel 66)
    See reel 88 for release
  - Clarence Hornung--Claim, undated (Reel 88)
  - Clyde Bartel, undated (Reel 128)
  - Court orders, garnishees, judgments, 1937-1938 (Reel 70)
  - Cream of Wheat--Federal Trade Commission, 1936 (Reel 81)
  - Cream of Wheat--Smith claim, 1939 (Reel 66)
  - Debonairs claim, 1938 (Reel 86)
  - Donald Hurley, undated (Reel 128)
  - Edgar Bergen--Licensing agreements and correspondence, 1937-1938 (Reel 86)
  - Edward Duffy, undated (Reel 128)
  - Edward Fuller--Fuller v. Esty, 1932-1936 (Reel 86)
  - Elgin National Watch--Crown Sales v. Elgin, 1944 (Reel 248)
  - Elgin National Watch--Jean Wheeler Jellico claim, 1944 (Reel 248)
  - Elgin National Watch--Watch Co. and Blue Network, 1944 (Reel 248)
  - Emerson Drug--"Neon Brain" picture, Dr. Edith Klemperer claim, 1936-1939 (Reel 88)
  - Emerson Drug--"Neon Brain" picture, Dr. Edith Klemperer claim, 1939 (Reel 248)
  - Emerson Drug--"Neon Brain" picture, Dr. Edith Klemperer claim, 1939-1940 (Reel 66)
  - Emily Watson Inc., 1937 (Reel 88)
  - Fidelio Brewery, undated (Reel 88)
  - Financial statements from creditors, through 1937 (Reel 86)
  - Fleischmann--Aklfred Kreymborg claim, 1933 (Reel 86)
  - Fleischmann--Clayton F. Summy Co. claim, 1934 (Reel 86)
  - Francis McArdle, undated (Reel 128)
    Payment of life insurance premiums due
  - General Cigar v. Merendi, 1939-1940 (Reel 66)
  - General Cigar--Lost sketch of Father's Day advertisement, 1942 (Reel 249)
  - George Fowler--Fowler v. Statesbury, 1925-1928 (Reel 86)
  - Goodwill Court, 1936-1937 (Reel 66)
  - Gorham, undated (Reel 88)
  - Gorham, undated (Reel 248)
  - Gorham--Cone v. JWT 1937-1939 (Reel 66)
    See reel 74, discontinued accounts; reel 87, letter of terms; reels 88, 248 signed releases
  - Grace McMaster, undated (Reel 128)
  - Griesedieck Western Brewery (St. Louis)--Mr. Malloy claim, "Stag Quizmaster", 1940 (Reel 249)
  - H.R. Lounsberry situation, 1931 (Reel 86)
  - Immigration--Extension of stay in U.S. for foreign employees, 1937-1938 (Reel 70)
  - Industrial Alcohol Institute--Claim of Consolidated Motor Bus Lines, 1929 (Reel 66)
    See reel 88 for release; reel 87 letter of terms
  - Industrial Alcohol Institute--Consolidated Motor Bus Lines, 1929 (Reel 88)
  - Isaace claim, undated (Reel 78)
  - J. Leonard Michelson, undated (Reel 78)
    Selling Idea and Advertising Plan for Gasoline
  - J.B. Williams--B.A. Dewey claim, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - J.B. Williams--Douglas Rolf claim, 1940 (Reel 249)
  - John Marshall Barbour claim, 1930 (Reel 86)
  - JWT withdrawal from St. Louis, undated (Reel 70)
  - Kathleen Malone (Mammy Goose radio), 1930-1935 (Reel 86)
  - Kraft-Phoenix Cheese, 1937-1938 (Reel 248)
  - Kraft-Phoenix Cheese--Reimer claim, 1940 (Reel 249)
  - Leila Leeds, undated (Reel 128)
  - Lever Brothers, 1937-1940 (Reel 88)
  - Lever Brothers, 1940 (Reel 249)
  - Lever Brothers--Alicia Bradley to Actors Equity, 1937 (Reel 88)
  - Lever Brothers--Alicia Bradley to Actors Equity, 1937 (Reel 248)
  - Lever Brothers--Ann Pennington suit, 1928-1931 (Reel 81)
  - Lever Brothers--Ann Pennington suit, undated (Reel 88)
  - Lever Brothers--Federal Trade Commission, 1932-1936 (Reel 81)
  - Lever Brothers--Fred Morgan, 1933 (Reel 248)
  - Lever Brothers--Fred Morgan, 1935 (Reel 88)
  - Lever Brothers--Helen Lawson claim, The Brat, 1942 (Reel 248)
  - Lever Brothers--Osgood claim, 1940 (Reel 249)
  - Lever Brothers--Ziegfield Follies, CBS, Benton & Bowles, 1936 (Reel 81)
  - Lever--Farewell to Arms (Lux Radio Theatre), 1933 (Reel 66)
  - Lever--Fred Morgan claim, 1933 (Reel 66)